http://www.tropitone.com/california-privacy-policy/do-not-sell-my-info

Request a Quote
SpacesBalconyBarClubDeckDiningFiresideGazeboPatioPoolsidePublic GatheringRestaurantVIPStyleCafé Outdoor FurnitureContemporary FurnitureTraditional FurnitureTransitional FurnitureGroupsArzoBasta Sole® Umbrellas & CabanasBrazoCabana ClubCantosCorsicaCurveDistrictElanceEvoFITFireFlairImpressionsKORKahanaKenzoLa ScalaLaguna BeachLakesideMainSailMarconiMillenniaMontreuxMontreux IIMuirlandsOpenPalladianPrimeRadiusRavelloSambaShorelineSorrentoSouth BeachSpinnakerTablesTorinoTrelonTropi-Kai®ValoraVeerVelaCollectionBasta Sole® Umbrellas & CabanasCafeCastCast & Patterned Aluminum FurnitureCushionEZ SPAN™ SegmentsFire ProductsMarine Grade PolymerModular SeatingPadded SlingSite FurnishingsSlingStrap & Cross StrapTablesURComfort®WovenProductAccessory PiecesCabana Club AccessoriesLights & DécorDécor (Non-lighted)Décor (Lighted)Chaise Lounge AccessoriesPillows & BolstersOutdoor AccessoriesBenchesCabanasAluminum Cabanas / PavilionsChaise LoungesFurniture CoversModular Seating PiecesOutdoor Bar StoolsOutdoor FireFire AccessoriesFire MediaFire PitsConcrete Fire PitsOutdoor OttomansOutdoor Patio ChairsOutdoor Dining ChairsSide ChairsSwivel RockersSpa/Sand ChairsLounge ChairsAction LoungersSwivel LoungerSwivel Action LoungersReclinersDouble GlidersSofas & Love SeatsOutdoor Patio TablesDining TablesConcrete TablesADA Height TablesOttoman Height TablesAccent TablesCounter Height TablesBar Height TablesTable TopsPlantersPlanters (Non-lighted)Planters (Lighted)Picnic TablesPatio Umbrellas & Market UmbrellasAluminum Patio UmbrellasUmbrella BasesWaste ReceptaclesBoulevard ReceptaclesRadiance ReceptaclesDistrict ReceptaclesSwatchFinishesFabricsSegments & Vinyls
Home > California Privacy Policy
California Privacy Policy
California Privacy Policy
Last Revised on: January 1, 2020
This Privacy Policy for California Residents (“California Privacy Policy”) supplements the information contained in and is parallel in scope to Hormel’s Privacy Policy. Hormel Foods Corporations and its subsidiaries (“Hormel,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) has adopted this California Privacy Policy in accordance with the notice requirements under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018, as amended (“CCPA”), and any terms defined in the CCPA have the same meaning when used in this California Privacy Policy.
Definitions Specific to this Policy
The CCPA includes definitions for terms specific to this California Privacy Policy that do not apply to Hormel’s privacy policy, including the following terms:
“Personal Information” means information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household. Personal Information does not include publicly available information obtained from government records; deidentified or aggregated consumer information that cannot be reconstructed to identify you; any information covered under the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act or the California Financial Information Privacy Act, activities covered by the Fair Credit Reporting Act, or protected health information as defined under the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act.
“Sale” or “sell” means selling, renting, releasing, disclosing, disseminating, making available, transferring, or otherwise communicating orally, in writing, or by electronic or other means, a consumer’s personal information by the business to another business or a third party for monetary or other valuable consideration.
“Service Provider” means a sole proprietorship, partnership, limited liability company, corporation, association, or other legal entity that is organized or operated for the profit or financial benefit of its shareholders or other owners, that processes information on behalf of a business and to which the business discloses a consumer’s Personal Information for a business purpose pursuant to a written contract.
“Third Party” means a person or entity who is not a business that collects Personal Information from consumers, as defined in the CCPA, and to whom the business discloses a consumer’s Personal Information for a business purpose pursuant to a written contract.
The Personal Information We Collect and Disclose
The chart below shows the categories of Personal Information we may collect; examples of the type of Personal Information in each category; all types of sources from which each category of Personal Information is collected; the business purposes for which that category of Personal Information is collected; and all types of third parties with whom that category of Personal Information is shared. As this chart shows, we disclose certain Personal Information to third parties for a business purpose. We also sell certain Personal Information to third parties.
Category of Personal Information
Unique identifiers
Examples
Name, signature, address, telephone email, account name, online identifier, IP address
Types of Sources from which this Category of Personal Information Is Collected
-Directly from you via our website
-Direct communication with youh6
-Social media interaction with you
-Marketing agencies
Business Purposes for Collection
-Provide you with goods and services
-Managing your preferences
-To help you finalize your purchases if your cart is abandoned
-Customer service communications
-Offer Promotions
Types of Third Parties with Whom this Category of Personal Information is Sold or Disclosed
Disclosed:
-Business partners
-Service providers
Sold:-Marketing providers-Analytics providers-Social media
Category of Personal Information
Financial information
Examples
Credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information
Types of Sources from which this Category of Personal Information Is Collected
-Directly from you via our website
-Claims management providers
Business Purposes for Collection
-Complete transactions
-Offer services and discounts
-Process claims
-Prevent fraud
Types of Third Parties with Whom this Category of Personal Information is Sold or Disclosed
Disclosed
-Service providers
-Business partners
Sold:
–None
Category of Personal Information
Purchase history
Examples
Commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies
Types of Sources from which this Category of Personal Information Is Collected
-Directly from you via our website
-Direct communication with you
-Social media interaction with you
-Marketing agencies
Business Purposes for Collection
-Provide you with goods and services
-Invite participation in surveys and feedback
-Customer service communications
-Improve promotions
Types of Third Parties with Whom this Category of Personal Information is Sold or Disclosed
Disclosed:
-Business partners
-Service providers
Sold:
-Marketing providers
-Analytics providers
-Social media
Category of Personal Information
Internet activity
Examples
Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer’s interaction with an Internet Web site, application, or advertisement
Types of Sources from which this Category of Personal Information Is Collected
-Directly from you via our website
-Social media interaction with you
-Marketing agencies
Business Purposes for Collection
-Product feedback
-Remember your preferences and information
-Marketing communications
-To monitor our click through rate
-To improve the content of our messaging
-Improve functionality of our website
Types of Third Parties with Whom this Category of Personal Information is Sold or Disclosed
Disclosed:
-Business partners
-Service providers
Sold
-Marketing providers
-Analytics providers
-Social media
Category of Personal Information
Geolocation data
Examples
Geolocation data
Types of Sources from which this Category of Personal Information Is Collected
–Directly from you via our website
-Social media interaction with you
-Marketing agencies
Business Purposes for Collection
-Product feedback
-Marketing communications
-To improve the content of our messaging
Types of Third Parties with Whom this Category of Personal Information is Sold or Disclosed
Sold:
-Marketing providers
-Analytics providers
-Social media
Category of Personal Information
Inferences
Examples
Inferences drawn from any of the information identified in this subdivision to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes
Types of Sources from which this Category of Personal Information Is Collected
–Directly from you via our website
-Social media interaction with you
-Marketing agencies
Business Purposes for Collection
-Product feedback
-Managing your preferences
-Offer Promotions
Types of Third Parties with Whom this Category of Personal Information is Sold or Disclosed
Sold:
-Marketing providers
-Analytics providers
-Social media
We will not collect a category of Personal Information not listed above, or use any Personal Information collected in any of the above categories for a business purpose not listed above, without first providing you with notice.
You have the right to request certain information regarding the Personal Information we have collected about you in the preceding 12 months. You may make such a request up to twice in a 12-month span. Please note that there are circumstances in which we may not be able to comply with your request pursuant to the CCPA, including when we cannot verify your request or when there is a conflict with our own obligations to comply with other legal or regulatory requirements. We will notify you following submission of your request if this is the case.
If you would like to request (1) the categories of Personal Information collected about you; (2) the purpose behind the collection; (3) the categories of third parties to which you have sold or disclosed this data; and (4) the purpose for these sales or disclosures, click Request to Know or call 1-800-523-4635. The link will take you to an interactive webform that you can complete and submit to make a request for information that we will then verify; if you use the telephone number, you will be guided through a process that will allow you to submit a verifiable request.
If you would like to request the specific pieces of Personal Information we collected about you, click Request to Know or call 1-800-523-4635. The link will take you to an interactive webform that you can complete and submit to make a request for information that we will then verify; if you use the telephone number, you will be guided through a process that will allow you to submit a verifiable request.
Verification Process
In order to protect your information, we will confirm a requestor’s identity before responding to any request. To start the process, you must provide your name and email. We will ask you at least one question, and you must reply by email with the correct answer for each question based on your previous interaction with us. If we still cannot verify your identity as required by the CCPA, we will let you know and may ask additional questions. Otherwise, we will acknowledge your request and contact you later with our full response.
We will only send CCPA verification questions from californiaprivacy@hormel.com. Before sending a verification response, please double-check the email address. If you receive an email that appears to be from us but is not from our CCPA verification email address listed above, do not respond.
Any information we gather through this process will only be used for consumer verification, security procedures, or fraud-prevention. We will delete any verification information as soon as practical after processing your request.
Personal Information of Minors
We are proud of our online information and we strive to ensure we don’t offend people of any age. However, our online content is not intended for children or minors under the age of sixteen years. Accordingly, we do not store information from minors under the age of sixteen years. If you believe that a child has submitted personal information to us, please contact us at californiaprivacy@hormel.com and we will delete the information.
Deletion of Your Personal Information
You have the right to request that we delete certain Personal Information that we have collected. Please note that there are circumstances in which we may not be able to comply with your request pursuant to the CCPA, including when we cannot verify your request and/or when there is a conflict with our own obligations to comply with other legal or regulatory requirements. We will notify you following submission of your request if this is the case.
If you would like to request that we delete your Personal Information pursuant to the requirements of the CCPA, click Request to Delete or call 1-800-523-4635. The link will take you to an interactive webform that you can complete and submit to make a request for deletion that we will then verify; if you use the telephone number, you will be guided through a process that will allow you to submit a verifiable request.
Authorized Agents
You may designate an authorized agent to exercise your rights under the CCPA on your behalf.
Pursuant to the CCPA:
Only a business entity or natural person registered with the California Secretary of State may act as an authorized agent.
You must provide the authorized agent written permission to exercise your rights under the CCPA on your behalf.
We may deny a request from an authorized agent on your behalf if the authorized agent does not submit proof that he, she, or it has been authorized by you to act on your behalf if we request such proof, as permitted by the CCPA.
Even if you use an authorized agent to exercise your rights under the CCPA on your behalf, pursuant to the CCPA we may still require that you verify your own identity directly to us. This provision does not apply if you have provided with a power of attorney under California Probate Code sections 4000 to 4465.
Right to Opt-Out
You have the right to request that we do not sell Personal Information that we have collected. If you exercise that right, please note that pursuant to the CCPA we may have to subsequently inform you that you need to opt-in if the sale of your Personal Information is required to complete a transaction you have initiated. If opting-in is required, we will provide you with the necessary instructions.
If you would like to request that we do not sell your Personal Information pursuant to the requirements of the CCPA, click Request to Opt Out or call 1-800-523-4635. The link will take you to an interactive webform that you can complete and submit to make a request for deletion; if you use the telephone number, you will be guided through a process that will allow you to submit a request.
If you use an authorized agent to submit your request to opt-out, we will request that the agent provide us with proof that he, she, or it has been authorized by you to act on your behalf. The CCPA requires you to provide the authorized agent written permission to exercise your rights under the CCPA.
If you opt-out of the sale of your Personal Information, we will wait at least 12 months before asking you if we may sell your Personal Information.
You have the right to opt-in to the sale of your Personal Information after you have opted out. If you would like to opt-in to the sale of your Personal Information, please email us at californiaprivacy@hormel.com or call us at 1-800-523-4635. Opting-in is a two-step process in which you will first clearly request to opt-in, and then separately confirm that choice.
Additional Information
If you would like additional information regarding our California Privacy Policy, please email us at californiaprivacy@hormel.com or call us at 1-800-523-4635.
Additional California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our web site that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to other parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request or to ask related questions, please contact us at:
Hormel Foods Corporation
1 Hormel Place
Austin, MN 55912
Attn: Legal Department
For information regarding our collection and use of data, please review Hormel’s Privacy Policy.
Changes to Our California Privacy Policy
Hormel reserves the right to amend this California Privacy Policy at our discretion and at any time. When we make changes to this California Privacy Policy, we will post an updated notice on our website with the effective date.
Return to the start of our California Privacy Policy.
Do not sell my info
Request For DeletionRequest To KnowRequests to Opt Out of the Sale of Personal Information
Swatch BookFinishesFabricsSegments & VinylsAbout UsWhy Tropitone?What's NewProduct CareGreen LivingEnjoyable LocationsBlogJoin the ListShopCatalogsVirtual ShowroomWhere to BuyServiceTrade AccountsAffiliatesContact UsWarrantyFAQSitemap
© 2020 Tropitone Furniture Company, Inc. A Brown Jordan International Company.
Privacy PolicyTerms of UseFull SiteDo Not Sell My Info
FacebookTwitterInstagramPinterestYouTubeGoogle+
Search
Select your experience.Choose one.Contract DesignerPurchasing ProfessionalcontractHomeownerResidential Designerresidential
Request a Quote
Browse By
